See?
I told you
even Mr. Famous would fall for it.
Now, let's start working on other painters
one by one.
All right.
Let's wet our whistles to celebrate!
You're talking like an old man.
What the heck?
Why do good beginnings always end badly?
- What?
- Wait.
What's going on?
Over there. That's Mr. Famous!
- It's Mr. Famous. Run.
- Mr. Famous is here?
This way.
Get down, James!
He's gone.
Is he gone now?
Mr. Kim…
What just happened?
Gosh, we almost got caught.
He didn't see us, right?
- No.
- Right, I don't think he saw us.
He didn't see us.
He saw us!
He must have! He's calling me.
- What the heck?
- Calm down.
We don't know what's going on yet.
You're an heir to a family empire.
- I'm an heir to a family empire.
- Exactly.
I'm the one with leverage.
- I'm the dominant one.
- Answer it.
MR. FAMOUS
Hello, Mr. Choi. This is Mr. Famous.
Yes, what is it?
- Wasn't that rude?
- No, it's fine.
- No? Did I sound okay?
- You sounded so polite!
If you're available tomorrow,
could I come see you at your place?
No, you're not available.
- I have to answer him.
- Say you can't.
No, wait!
Well…
There's a place I often go to.
Let's meet there.
See you tomorrow.
Please send me the address.
We don't have a house! What do we do now?
What's he planning?
Perhaps…
No way.
Did he find out?
EPISODE 4
Mr. Famous.
Do you know Kim Yong-bok?
Kim Yeon-bok...
Kim Yeon-bok…
Yeon-bok's the name
of a Chinese chef. Geez.
I asked if you knew a man
called Kim Yong-bok.
I'm not sure who Kim Yong-bok is…
My apologies
for not telling you in advance.
Why are you apologizing…
I'm sure you felt very uneasy
when I reported your painting.
I had to verify something.
I apologize again
for not informing you beforehand.
Honestly,
I'd be lying if I said
I didn't feel uneasy.
This won't get you involved
with the police
or put you in any trouble.
That's a relief.
But how did you know it was a forgery?
Well, to keep it short,
just like how everyone
has their own unique handwriting,
all painters have their own
unique brushstrokes.
Even the art forgers
have habits they can't hide.
You can never ignore experience.
I have data on all the art forgers
and art conservators in Korea.
I can see through all of them.
Any ordinary appraiser would have
fallen for it. But I'm Mr. Famous!
No one can fool me.
What's your opinion on appraisers?
Being an appraiser is not an easy job!
The history of appraisers
will start with me.
An appraiser doesn't only judge
if the artwork is real or not,
but also one's emotions…
Geez, that was exhausting.
He's so damn talkative.
We didn't think
he'd have data on art conservators.
Director of Gallery Fame
and seasoned art critic, Mr. Famous,
is drawing attention after revealing
that a recently sold Elcasso painting
was a forgery.
And now, several other forgeries
he previously identified
are receiving attention again.
Mr. Famous will only get more followers.
His clients will trust him even more.
We underestimated him.
We were completely wrong.
That's kind of true.
Kind of.
He needed a reputation
to make more money before the big event.
And we fell for it.
Wait. By big event…
do you mean this?
"A charity auction party."
He called to give you this.
Yeah. He told me…
It's time to play in the big leagues now.
- Let me invite you to said big leagues.
- Right.
Join us in the big leagues.
"It's time to play
in the big leagues, Mr. Choi."
"Join us in the big leagues."
Then, he gave that to me.
Yi-rang, are you listening?
Stop talking.
I'm going to get some sleep.
Don't wake me up.
She must be shocked.
Right.
We should give her some time, right?
I think so.
Yay, the fried chicken is here!
Fried chicken that's to die for!
Sweet and salty!
And crispy on the outside
and juicy on the inside!
Today, I got some
with special garlic sauce,
which will help boost your immune system.
There's no time to sleep.
Excessive drinking is bad for your liver.
So let's drink a lot!
- Cheers!
By the way, Yi-rang.
It's about time
you come up with the next plan.
Of course.
Yi-rang would never give up like this.
She would never.
I bet she came up
with an even more wicked plan.
For sure.
We'll find Mr. Famous's list.
Mr. Famous's list?
The artwork ledger
that Mr. Famous used for deals.
The root of the politicians' slush funds.
Right. But how are we going to find that?
We'll find the answer to that
at this party.
Neither Mr. Famous's house
nor his gallery had a place
to hide his weakness.
If they are Mr. Famous's public spaces,
this has to be his personal space.
All of his illegal conduct
is committed here.
It must be here somewhere.
The operation will begin.
Is everyone ready?
I'm ready, Boss. Let's do this, Olivia.
Just you wait, Mr. Famous.
Is this the performing artist's van?
Yes, is everything all right?
Are you the singer? It can't be you.
I'm not the singer.
Sir, I think you'll have
to show him your face.
But you're so handsome.
I almost didn't recognize you
without your wig.
Hello. I'm a fan of yours.
Don't you have a TV at home?
The director gave me special orders
to guide you.
Mr. Choi.
- Hello.
- Thank you for coming.
My pleasure.
And may I ask who this is?
This is the Head of Purchasing
for Wonderby Asia,
Olivia Kim.
I see.
I've heard much about you.
I'm Choi Seung-chan from LHC.
It's an honor to meet you.
The honor is mine.
I would have never imagined meeting
such a beautiful lady like you.
I will take that as a compliment.
I have someone to introduce you to.
Come with me.
- What's with that nasally voice?
- What's with that cheesy speech?
What?
You must be tired. Get some rest.
I'll find a way to handle the performance.
I got the invitation. I'm going in.
Now,
we will begin the special auction.
The first painting was donated
by Mrs. Na Mi-hee,
the wife of the leader
of the Jinpureun Party.
Ma'am.
There's nothing special about it.
Why is everyone so amazed?
It's a fascinating work.
We'll start from seven million.
Seven million.
Eight million.
Nine million.
Ten million.
How high will it go?
Hey, Yi-rang. Shouldn't I bid too?
Don't do anything stupid.
Now, we'll raise the bid increment
from millions to the tens of millions.
Twenty million.
I'm bidding.
Thirty million.
- What's wrong with him?
- Forty million.
Fifty million.
Eighty million.
One hundred million.
Now, we'll raise the bid increment
to 50 million.
One hundred and fifty million.
Two hundred million.
Two hundred and fifty million.
Three hundred million.
Three hundred and fifty million.
Four hundred million.
Four hundred and fifty million.
Five hundred million.
Anyone for 500 million?
Suit yourself.
Anyone else for 500 million?
Then…
Five hundred million.
Five hundred million!
What a relief.
Sold for 500 million.
Congratulations.
- Please follow my manager for assistance.
- Hey, Yi-rang.
Why are the two leaving together?
It's creating a chance to bribe
in the name of a charity auction.
So basically, big spenders
get their favors granted.
Is that how it works?
That's right.
My goodness. This is just perfect.
Here is the last painting.
It was donated by the chairman
of Hundred Victories Group.
His wife is present tonight.
Okay, then.
I will reveal the artwork.
The Intangible Cultural Heritage
Number Two,
the Maltugi Tal
of Yangju Byeolsandae Nori.
What? Kkolttugi?
It was created in the late Joseon Dynasty.
And it couldn't be
in any better condition.
The bid starts from 100 million.
What?
One hundred million.
Two hundred million.
- Are they buying it for real?
- Five hundred million.
Eight hundred million.
One billion.
One and a half billion.
Two billion.
Two and a half billion.
Three billion.
Hey.
Are you trying to pull the same stunt?
Seriously?
Anyone for three billion?
Three billion.
Three and a half billion.
Sold for 3.5 billion.
Thank goodness.
Congratulations.
We've prepared an after-party.
- I hope you enjoy.
- Three billion, for goodness' sake.
He could make several hundred million won
overnight just from commission.
Okay, I got his fingerprint.
I got the password!
Password secured.
Behind the frame next to the desk.
Darn.
Hey.
You shouldn't have.
I brought snacks to keep your spirits up.
- Come in.
- Sure.
- The director told me…
- Yeah.
…to get you non-alcoholic drinks.
- Non-alcohol?
- What a considerate man.
CONTROL ROOM
The control room has been taken care of.
What's wrong?
Are you okay, Olivia?
Geez. What is she doing
in the middle of an operation?
Do you want to get some fresh air outside?
Shall we?
Let's do that then.
I feel lightheaded.
Oh, boy.
I'm sorry. Be careful.
Gosh, you flatter me.
I'm sorry. I couldn't stop myself.
I should've held back.
Olivia.
Holding back will make you sick.
Don't hold back.
What's that?
Security! Run to my office! Hurry!
Yes, sir.
What the…
I found it.
I got it.
Something wrong?
Olivia.
It's dangerous.
Stay right here.
I'll be right back.
Where are you?
- Get out of there now.
- Not yet.
Wait.
James, buy me more time.
What? I can't hear you.
What? Stop them?
Where are they?
Got it.
To the right!
Jump!
Jump higher!
Okay! Jump!
Damn it.
Check the control room.
Yes, sir.
What the heck?
Damn it.
Hey. Wake up.
I think it's all been deleted.
- Hey, check that too.
- Okay.
Hey, who are you?
That hurts.
CONTROL ROOM
What's all this noise?
Hey, what are you two doing?
Still partying.
Damn it.
Should I call the police?
Are you trying to tell everyone
that we got robbed?
If I lose the VVIPs' trust,
how are you going to make up for that?
I'm sorry, sir.
What's that car?
Stop that car. Now!
- Stop that car!
- Yes, sir.
Thank you for coming.
Get home safely. Goodbye.
Here.
Are you sure you're okay?
It's nothing.
I'm glad to hear that.
Mr. Famous.
Thank you.
- Good night, then.
- Good night.
Should I turn the heat on?
Yeah, to level four.
That's not the heat control.
I thought it was.
It's on.
Oh, it's warm.
At least let me change my shoes.
Come on.
- I'm drained.
- Geez.
Why take off your heels--
- I think I got a cold from Mr. Famous.
- Hey.
- Geez. Thanks.
- This way. Careful.
Goodness.
Good.
I'm thirsty.
Guys, you want something to drink?
Yeah. Maybe chamomile tea.
No, just drink water.
Gosh, that was really close.
Let's see what's in this.
FAME WORK TRANSACTION LEDGER
- Oh, boy.
- Gosh, I'm so tired.
Seriously, that was so close.
This is a huge list.
Really?
Let's check out the VIPs
in league with Mr. Famous.
This isn't a transaction history though.
"M27CH dash one." What's that?
M and F.
So, male and female.
Male, 27 years old?
What's this?
What is this?
Gosh, this jerk.
He's an even bigger piece of trash.
What kind of ridiculous situation is this?
Would you believe me if I said
even bigger works have been created
by my own hands?
So he's locking up naive, obscure painters
and running a forgery factory.
Wait.
Kim Bo-ra. 23 years old. Kim…
Bo-ra.
Hey, stop watching.
JAEHAN UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
Bo-ra.
Are you feeling better?
Hey, your mother is worried
because you're not eating.
You should at least pretend to eat
for your mother. Okay?
It's cold today.
Do you want to go back inside?
I'll go first and talk with your mother.
Take your time.
Gu-ho.
Mr. Famous…
He said he'd take a look at my paintings,
so I went to see him.
You're here, Bo-ra.
It's me.
You've gotten better from last time.
Really?
You're improving every day.
Bo-ra.
Yes?
How about working
as an intern artist at my company?
An intern artist?
After the internship,
I'd like to open an exhibition
for people with talent.
An exhibition?
An exhibition.
You could totally be one of them.
You're so pretty.
A debut exhibition at Gallery Fame.
It was the best bait for students like me.
I had to endure it.
I thought that was the only way for me
to open an exhibition
and debut as an artist.
But…
You scumbag!
I did everything you said.
Wasn't that enough for you?
The exhibition.
You said you'd open it for me.
This really is the last time!
My hand is not listening to me!
But I have to be in the exhibition.
Professor!
- I finished it!
- How long do I have to keep painting?
So please stop this!
- Everyone was going insane.
- Let me out of here!
And my body was breaking down…
in that short period of time.
I kept telling myself to get it together…
but it was no use.
That kind Mr. Famous
when he was tossing the bait
was long gone.
Hey, watch it.
I kept hearing there were minor mistakes.
I guess it was your work.
No, Mr. Famous.
If I get some sleep, I'll be okay.
Sleep isn't the issue.
The issue is your skills.
But I've been doing well until now.
I've been working really hard.
- Now, the exhibition--
- What?
Exhibition?
Hey.
Do you think you've become a real artist
because you're painting here?
With your disgusting and pathetic skills?
You think any damn fool
can hold an exhibition?
It's tragic to put in all that effort
with zero talent.
But you definitely said I had talent then.
"Not bad."
"You've improved since the last time."
Do any of those words mean talent?
I'll be good.
I swear I can be good. Please!
Give me one more chance!
Geez, for Christ's sake.
I can show you now.
Show me what?
Hey, just get lost.
Stop ruining my paintings.
Geez.
And don't do anything stupid.
The security camera caught you...
taking the drugs on your own.
If you want to call the cops, do it.
Then, you'll become a drug offender.
Your mom will be happy to hear
that her daughter is a junkie.
What? Exhibition?
Do you think you've become a real artist
because you're painting here?
With your disgusting and pathetic skills?
You think any damn fool
can hold an exhibition?
It's tragic to put in all that effort
with zero talent.
Hey, Kim Bo-ra.
Kim Bo-ra!
No!
Hey, are you okay?
Hey, Bo-ra. Come on.
That damn scumbag.
So? How's Purple doing?
She's just spaced out all day.
Gosh, it must be tough.
She was hurt by the work she loves to do.
That scum of the earth takes advantage
of innocent passion for his own gain!
I'm going to stomp all over him.
This must be it!
Bo-ra's mom's side dish trifecta?
Aren't you supposed to ask
how Bo-ra is doing like James did?
James already asked.
What's this? I've never seen this before.
Is this kimchi?
It's fermented flounder.
Bo-ra's mother's family
is from Hamgyong Province.
That's where they learned the recipe.
It's not bad. It's tasty.
- It's pure art.
- Right?
What did you just say?
Nothing.
He didn't say anything.
That's it!
They don't match the interior design
of the villa I'm moving to.
Still, there's more artwork
than I expected.
Let me take a closer look.
Did your daughter draw this one?
Just kidding.
That little…
You should get rid
of all these pieces here.
They don't suit you.
You can't just accept everything
that comes your way.
They're cracked and broken.
It's like pouring water
into a bottomless jar.
Mr. Choi, is this…
Oh, that.
That's from 1933.
The Sight of the Sea.
The name of the painter
is Cheon Myeong-shin.
That name sounds familiar.
It's beautiful.
It's so beautiful that it's making me cry.
What year did you say?
It's from 1933.
From...
1933?
From 1933?
The next artwork has an interesting story.
Perhaps,
this is a very valuable piece.
Piece number 23.
The Sight of the Sea
by Cheon Myeong-shin.
It's from 1933.
It's an oil painting.
Dimensions are 61 by 50 centimeters.
The main thing to focus on is the period
in which this was drawn, which is 1933.
That was during
the Japanese occupation period.
Unlike other countries that accepted
various European painting styles slowly,
many painting styles
swarmed into Korea all at once,
so it wasn't easy for each style
to mature during that time.
However,
there is always one genius in every era.
During that difficult period,
one obscure painter we weren't aware of
used strong brushstrokes and vivid colors.
Like Fauvism and Cubism,
as if van Gogh and Cezanne were mixed.
And the artist has
a unique, delicate touch.
To me, it was a refreshing jolt.
Now, the decision is up to you.
The bid price starts...
from 15 million won.
Fifteen million.
Sixteen million.
Seventeen million.
Eighteen million.
Nineteen million.
Twenty million.
We'll raise the bid increment
to 10 million.
Thirty million.
- Forty--
- One hundred million.
We have 100 million.
Anyone else?
One hundred million.
Sold!
In all honesty,
I never expected you
to say 100 million just like that.
Let's call it an investment.
Do you think there's only one painting
done by this artist?
When this painting was put up for auction,
the seller probably
had another plan in mind.
I keep thinking…
we could become the best partners ever.
What are you talking about?
KOREAN ART'S HIDDEN GEM FOUND
BY DIRECTOR OF GALLERY FAME
AND ART CRITIC, MR. FAMOUS
I'm an investor.
Do you think there's only one painting
done by this artist?
If Wonderby purchases all the pieces
by Cheon Myeong-shin,
the profit will be enormous.
Secretary Kim, it's me.
Look up Cheon Myeong-shin's paintings.
Now that I threw the bait,
there should be a bite.
Sir!
I got a call that someone
has a similar painting.
Really?
When I got the call,
I searched thoroughly,
like I was combing for lice.
So?
Is it one of his paintings?
Sensual texture. Dizzying colors.
This was definitely painted
by Cheon Myeong-shin.
Sir.
Let me take this painting over.
I'll pay you triple.
Do you have any information
about this painting?
I thought I saw something
written on the back.
Oh, there it is.
CHEON JONG-YEOP
EUNGSAN-EUP, PAEJU-SI
Excuse me.
Mr. Cheon Jong-yeop? Are you inside?
I came down from Seoul.
- What do you want?
- Geez!
Gosh!
Were you peeping in to see
if there was anything to steal?
Mr. Cheon Jong-yeop?
Thank you.
Right. Thank you.
Every guest who visits my house
must drink one.
It's the rule and a rite of passage.
I selected only the good herbs
and boiled them in the cauldron.
I did it myself.
It's good for there.
There?
I mean, down there.
Do I have to say it? Geez.
Down there.
I see. Down there.
Down there. Right.
Drink.
Geez, how disgusting.
It reeks.
Drink up.
I…
- It's a rite of passage.
- Okay.
- You've passed.
- Thank you.
By chance,
do you happen to know Cheon Myeong-shin?
Let me think.
Myeong-shin. Cheon Myeong-shin.
That sounds familiar… Yes!
Yes?
Why are you looking for my aunt?
Well, then…
are any of her paintings here…
Oh, my. How did you know
that she was a dauber?
- Yes, here it is.
- Okay.
I guess she was born in 1919.
Sir, by any chance,
could I see her paintings?
She was born frail during difficult times.
I heard she came close
to death many times.
But I guess she painted a lot.
It seems she won awards at primary school.
Goodness, but what's the point?
She was born to a poor family,
and she was in poor health.
At the time,
canvases and paint cost a lot.
To prepare painting materials,
she delivered milk
when she wasn't even well,
and she even did piles of laundry
until her hands were all swollen.
That year, when it snowed
an insane amount,
she went out to deliver milk
and never came back.
So we went out to find her,
and that's what happened.
Aunt Myeong-shin, you have a visitor.
Are these all her paintings?
There's an unnecessary amount,
isn't there?
How were so many pieces painted
in such a short time?
Gosh, it was such an ordeal.
Pardon?
I mean,
she kept painting without eating properly.
So imagine what happened to her stomach.
Of course, it'd be an ordeal for her.
Right.
Would it or wouldn't it be an ordeal?
It would. Yes.
Sir.
I will purchase...
all these paintings.
My goodness. What for?
I can give you 100 million won.
How does it sound?
My goodness.
Stop joking around.
Do you think I'm an idiot?
Then, I'll double it
and give you 200 million.
Forget it.
I'll trade them for taffies later.
Then, ten million for each work.
I'll give you 300 million.
Three hundred million.
My goodness. Is this really happening?
Then, I will…
How about three billion won, sir?
Three billion?
Olivia, how did you find this place?
You left in a rush, so I tailed you.
Are these
all Cheon Myeong-shin's paintings?
Miss, did you just say three billion?
Yes, three billion.
Three billion isn't much
for beautiful paintings like these.
Hold on, sir.
You can spend that much
without your company's approval?
I know it's Wonderby,
but don't they have procedures?
My, what a shame.
Mr. Choi? But why…
You told me to play in the big leagues.
So I decided to make an investment.
Hello.
Who is this man now?
They say vices learned late in life
are the worst and you two just…
Hold on!
You just said three billion…
Three and a half billion!
Three and a half?
Sir, calm down and listen to me.
This person is just a buyer from abroad.
She'll be sending all these precious works
- to foreign countries.
- What?
Sir, to this man,
paintings are just money.
You saw it yourself.
He offered only 100 million for all of…
Seriously, how shameless.
- Right. Earlier, he said…
- Damn it!
Olivia, you seriously
have it wrong right now.
But you're a buyer, not an appraiser.
Turning an amateur painter
from the countryside into van Gogh.
Only I,
Mr. Famous can do that.
Got it?
Gosh, if you're that good,
why don't you be van Gogh yourself then?
Sir.
Let me settle this for you.
I'll buy all
of Cheon Myeong-shin's precious works
for four billion won.
Four billion?
Four and a half billion.
Four and a half billion!
- Five billion!
- Five…
For goodness' sake!
What a shame.
Yes, five billion.
Sold.
In today's auction,
we'll only feature the works
of an obscure painter
who hasn't been widely discovered yet.
This marks the birth of a new star
in the Korean art scene.
The late Cheon Myeong-shin
was a passionate artist
who poured her soul into painting
while battling illness
during the Japanese occupation period.
Her bold drawings and powerful strokes
capture her aching desire to live
in this masterpiece!
Hey, that's me.
What?
Please remain silent. Thank you.
I said I'm Cheon Myeong-shin.
I'm not a genius painter
who died at a young age.
I'm a small business owner who runs
Cheonmyeongshin Shop by the beach.
I wasn't born in 1919. I was born in 1964,
the Year of the Dragon.
I am the mother
of Kim Bo-ra, my dear daughter.
Kim Bo-ra?
So, did you enjoy admiring my paintings?
Your paintings?
These are all your works?
How?
We'll make her a real artist! A real one!
Then, the paintings will be real,
because they're done by a real artist.
- A real artist!
Well, it wasn't your fault
you were bitten by a rabid dog.
But whether you fall apart like this
or get back on your feet
is up to you.
Sleep on it.
78 DOKSIMNI, MUN-GU, SEOUL
ANTIQUE ART SHOP
Look here. Yes, very nice.
Let's see.
- Pretty good, right?
- It's a really good picture.
All right.
I was worried
just in case you'd recognize it.
I guess you really admired my talent.
I painted all of them, everyone.
- What's going on?
- He's a swindler!
So this was all a scam?
Historical moment, my foot.
What kind of trick
are you trying to pull on us?
That damn junkie must still be high.
How dare she come in here?
Hey, you little…
How dare you lay your hand
on my precious daughter?
I'll cut it off
and turn it into radish kimchi!
- What's that?
- My goodness!
Are they painting forgeries?
How is that possible?
What…
Show me what?
Just get lost. Stop ruining my paintings.
No.
No!
What's going on?
Oh my!
- What's he doing?
- My goodness.
Oh, dear.
How pathetic.
No. This isn't true!
This was all fabricated.
It's a deepfake!
That's AI. That's not me!
Mr. Famous.
You're Mr. Famous, right?
What now?
We received a report.
A report?
You're under arrest
for abduction, confinement,
blackmailing,
and the distribution and sale of drugs.
You have the right to remain silent.
You have the right to an attorney.
Anything you say can and will be used
against you in a court of law.
Who are you to arrest me?
Who do you think you are?
We can talk later.
- I'm Mr. Famous.
- Take him.
I'm Mr. Famous. Don't you know who I am?
Hey! I'm Mr. Famous!
Just you wait.
You filthy little…
Gosh.
- Goodness.
- It smells amazing.
- Be careful.
- No, I got it. Call the kids.
Hey, come here!
The ramyeon will get soggy!
Guys, let's run! Let's go eat ramyeon!
I thought Gu-ho was just a clumsy guy
with a handsome face.
But he's actually pretty amazing.
I know. I see him in a new light now.
How about him as husband material?
What are you talking about?
- What? He's not so bad.
- No.
Is that really a no?
Absolutely not.
Really?
- Bon appetit!
- You lost, so you can't eat.
- No, stop it.
No, I won.
We scored three goals.
- He's right.
- Right, you scored two.
- And I scored one.
- No, we…
FAME WORK TRANSACTION LEDGER
YU KANG-IL, GHOST CASTLE
EMPTY TRASH
DO NOT ENTER
We should've suspected it.
We should've seen if he was
a real doctor or just a damn fraud.
Are we supposed to let the kid die?
You think we'll be the only ones
getting screwed?
She didn't die during surgery.
Isn't that enough?
If we got a good scene
for our hospital's promotional video,
she's run out of use, you idiot.
How are we going to make them pay?
Okay. The codename for this operation
will be "Eye and Tooth."
An eye for an eye, a tooth for a tooth.
I'll make sure she experiences fire
and brimstone even in the dead of winter.